bugaboo.com 2014-06-18

# Bugaboo - Privacy Policy

**PRIVACY STATEMENT OF BUGABOO INTERNATIONAL B.V.**

Bugaboo respects your privacy. We therefore deal carefully with your personal data. We make every effort to guarantee the reliability, security and integrity of the data that we gather. Personal data is processed in a manner that complies with the requirements set by the Dutch Personal Data Protection Act.

Bugaboo respects your privacy. We therefore deal carefully with your personal data. We make every effort to guarantee the reliability, security and integrity of the data that we gather. Personal data is processed in a manner that complies with the requirements set by the Dutch Personal Data Protection Act.

**How do we use your personal data?**

By providing your personal data, you consent to us using this data in order to comply with our obligations to you and to offer the service that you expect of us. This includes processing and dispatching orders, sending delivery status e-mails, managing your account by carrying out credit checks or informing you about a safety risk relating to one of our products. If any problem arises with the delivery of your order, we shall also use this data to contact you. We do not store your data for longer than is necessary to perform our services, or only for as long as we are obliged to do so by law.

**Who has access to the data?**

Bugaboo only sends data to third parties in order to comply with our obligations towards you. Bugaboo sends your data, for instance, to suppliers and mail order partners in connection with the dispatch of goods. Bugaboo may also pass on your data to organisations such as credit rating or collection agencies for the purpose of credit checks, ID checks, keeping track of creditworthiness and for debt collections.

**How do we protect your data?**

We have adopted both technical and organisational measures to protect your data against loss, manipulation, unauthorised access, etc. We continually improve our security measures in case of technological advances and developments. We kindly request you to properly and correctly secure your own electronic data carrier.

**Credit card payments**

In order to make credit card payments to us as secure as possible, all information is sent in encrypted form using SSL (Secure Sockets Layer). This means that the information is sent through a secure connection and that your credit card details cannot be seen by external parties.  
In order to make credit card payments to us as secure as possible, all information is sent in encrypted form using SSL (Secure Sockets Layer). This means that the information is sent through a secure connection and that your credit card details cannot be seen by external parties.

**Cookies**

When you use Bugaboo websites, Bugaboo and/or third parties may gather information about your use of this and other websites, for instance by means of cookies. A cookie is a small file that is sent along with pages of a website and stored on your computer hard drive by your browser. The cookie then allows your browser to be recognised when you make repeated visits to a website.

The information that Bugaboo and/or third parties gather, for instance by means of cookies, may be used for the following purposes:

  1. For functional purposes: to facilitate logging into or navigating Bugaboo websites or to remember your settings and/or preferences when using Bugaboo websites.  
Example: you log into a website and our system knows via a cookie that you are logged in upon your next visit to the same website. You therefore do not have to login again.

  2. For analytical purposes: in order to analyse the use of Bugaboo websites.  
Example: record can be kept of how many visitors visit a specific web page, so that Bugaboo knows which of its websites, or parts of its websites, are popular.

  3. 3\. For commercial purposes: to keep record of how many and which advertisements you are shown (i.e. to prevent you from always seeing the same advertisement) and to be able to check whether you have clicked on an advertisement.  
Example: you may be shown a commercial for a video. In order to prevent you from seeing the same commercial each time, a record can be kept of the commercials that have already been shown to you.

  4. 4\. For targeting purposes: in order to build up a profile of you, based on your web-browsing behaviour, so that advertisements which are matched to your existing and probable interests can be displayed. This profile can also be built up on the basis of information of your visits to other websites.

The information gathered by Bugaboo based on the above can be combined with the personal data processed by Bugaboo. However, the information gathered by third parties is not linked to the personal data processed by Bugaboo. Bugaboo does not make use of and has no access to this information gathered by third parties. The use of cookies and other techniques by these third parties, as referred to above, is subject to their own privacy policy, which is mostly set out on their own website(s).

| 

**Deletion and refusal of cookies**

You can delete existing cookies and refuse to accept new cookies via the browser settings on your computer. The manner in which this is done differs from browser to browser. Use the help function of your browser, if necessary. You can also individually or collectively refuse to accept most cookies that are placed when using Bugaboo websites via <http://www.youronlinechoices.com/uk/your-ad-choices>. You can also see which of the listed cookies are active on your browser here.

After deleting and/or refusing to accept cookies, you can still continue to see advertisements.

NB: if you refuse to accept and/or delete cookies, you will not always be able to make full use of a website's features. The refusal to accept and/or deletion of cookies only apply to the computer and the browser on which you perform this action. If you make use of several computers and/or browsers, you will need to perform the aforementioned action(s) as often as necessary.

**Links**

Our website bugaboo.com contains links to other websites over which we have no control. We do not accept any liability for the protection of personal data on or for the content of these websites; we simply offer these links to make it easier for our visitors to find more information about specific topics.

**Inspection, correction and right of objection**

If you have a relationship with our company, you may inspect your personal data following a written request to that effect. If the summary provided by us contains inaccuracies, you may request us in writing to amend or delete the data. You may also notify us if you do not wish to be approached with information about our products and services, in writing to the following address:

Paasheuvelweg 9a-b  
1105 BE Amsterdam

If you have subscribed to our newsletter, you may always unsubscribe by sending an e-mail to [service.uk@bugaboo.com](mailto:service.uk@bugaboo.com). We shall then not send you any further mailings.

**Amendment of Privacy Statement**

We reserve the right to amend this privacy statement. Amendments will be published on this website.

**Copyright**

The content of this website is protected by copyright and is the property of Bugaboo International B.V.  
  
---|---
